Guide to the C. Darwin Stolzenbach papers, 1930-1988 MS2028
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Miscellaneous, 1950-1979; MS2028 Series 4; 18 Linear feet
  - Newspaper Clippings: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Newspaper Clippings: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Newspaper Clippings: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper Clippings: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper Clippings: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Newspaper Clippings: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper Clippings: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Newspaper Clippings: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Newspaper Clippings: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper Clippings: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Public Hearings: on 1-266, 1970 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Public Hearings: on 1-266, 1970 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Public Hearings: on 1-266, 1970 December 14 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Public Hearings: on 1-266, 1970 December 14 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Public Hearings: on 1-266, 1970 December 14 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Public Hearings: on 1-266, 1970 December 14 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Public Hearings: on 1-266, 1970 December 15 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Public Hearings: on 1-266, 1970 December 15 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Public Hearings: on 1-266, 1970 December 15 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Public Hearings: on 1-266, 1970 December 15 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Public Hearings: on 1-266, 1970 December 15 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Public Hearings: on 1-266, 1970 December 16 (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Public Hearings on 1-266, 1970 December 14-16 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Public Hearings on 1-266, 1970 December 14-16 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Public Hearings on 1-266, 1970 December 14-16 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Public Hearings on 1-266, 1970 December 14-16 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Reading Files: Harland Bartholomew Reading File, 1956-1959 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Reading Files: Harland Bartholomew Reading File, 1956-1959 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Reading Files: Harland Bartholomew Reading File, 1956-1959 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Reading Files: Harland Bartholomew Reading File, 1956-1959 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Reading Files: Harland Bartholomew Reading File, 1956-1959 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Reading Files: Harland Bartholomew Reading File, 1956-1959 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Reading Files: Committee of 100 Reading File, 1967-1972 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Reading Files: Committee of 100 Reading File, 1967-1972 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Reading Files: Committee of 100 Reading File, 1967-1972 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Reading Files: Committee of 100 Reading File, 1967-1972 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Reading Files: Committee of 100 Reading File, 1967-1972 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Reading Files: Committee of 100 Reading File, 1967-1972 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Reading Files: Committee of 100 Reading File, 1967-1972 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Reading Files: Jackson Graham Reading File, 1969-1973 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - Reading Files: Jackson Graham Reading File, 1969-1973 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Reading Files: Jackson Graham Reading File, 1969-1973 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Reading Files: Jackson Graham Reading File, 1969-1973 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Reading Files: Jackson Graham Reading File, 1969-1973 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Reading Files: Senator Charles A. Horsky Reading File, 1962-1966 (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - Reading Files: Senator Charles A. Horsky Reading File, 1962-1966 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Reading Files: Senator Charles A. Horsky Reading File, 1962-1966 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Reading Files: Congressman Carlton Sickles Reading File, 1963-1965 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Reading Files: Congressman Carlton Sickles Reading File, 1963-1965 (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - Reading Files: Paul Sitton Reading File, 1958-1964 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Reading Files: Paul Sitton Reading File, 1958-1964 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Reading Files: Paul Sitton Reading File, 1958-1964 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Reading Files: Paul Sitton Reading File, 1958-1964 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Reading Files: Paul Sitton Reading File, 1958-1964 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Reading Files: Paul Sitton Reading File, 1958-1964 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Reading Files: Paul Sitton Reading File, 1958-1964 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Reports: Air Pollution, Reports, undated (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Reports: Air Quality Criteria for Carbon Monoxide, 1970 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Reports: Arlington County Board Statement on Environmental Impact of Proposed Interstate Route 66, 1972 January (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Reports: "Benefits of Interstate Highways", undated (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - Reports: The Bicentennial Celebration in the National Capital Region, 1976 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Reports: Budget Estimates of the District of Columbia, 1966 January (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Reports: Budget of the United States Government, District of Columbia, 1968 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Reports: Budget of the United States Government, District of Columbia, 1969 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Reports: "Carbon Monoxide Study for the Proposed Three Sisters Bridge, 1971 January (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Reports: Chronology of Three Sisters Bridge Development, 1970 May (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Reports: Citizens Advisory Committee on Recreation and Natural Beauty, 1967 June (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Reports: Conference on New Approaches to Urban Transportation, 1967 November (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Reports: Department of Highways and Traffic, Recommendations, undated (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Reports: Design Study Report, Interstate Route 266, 1971 April (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Reports: "Evolution of the DC Highway System,", 1971 June (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Reports: Factors Affecting the Lengthy Process of Planning Highways, 1972 March (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Reports: Financial Services, Portfolios, undated (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Reports: Financial Services, Portfolios, undated (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Reports: Financial Services, Portfolios, undated (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Reports: The First Four Years of Metrorail-Travel Changes, 1981 September (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Reports: John Hodges, "Fourth Annual Institute on Motor Vehicle and Traffic Law,", 1972 August (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Reports: Georgetown Waterfront Area Study, 1971 January (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Reports: Georgetown Waterfront Feasibility Study, undated (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Reports: "Highway Environment Reference Book,", 1970 November (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Reports: House Debate and Report on HR 17134, Federal-Aid Highway Act of 1968, undated (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Reports: "Interstate Substitutions. A Handbook for Mayors", undated (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Reports: "Metrorail Alternatives Analysis," Final Analysis, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Reports: National Capital Planning Commission Comprehensive Plan for the National Capital, 1968 December (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Reports: 1972 National Transportation Report, 1972 July (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Reports: Office of the Assistant Secretary for Environment and Urban Systems, "Research Program Summary,", 1971 January (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - Reports: Park and Recreational Facilities, undated (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - Reports: Process Report, Critical Path Procedures, undated (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - Reports: Proposed Three Sisters Bridge. Type, Size, and Location Report, 1970 May (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - Reports: Report and Recommendations of Transportation Committee, 1971 December (Box 76, Folder 17)
  - Reports: Report to Congress on Withheld Reimbursements of the Federal-Aid Highway Program, 1967 July (Box 76, Folder 18)
  - Reports: Reports to Congress, undated (Box 76, Folder 19)
  - Reports: Social Patterns and Attitudes in Greater Washington, 1973-1975 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Reports: Staff Draft, "Comprehensive Plan for the National Capital,", 1968 November (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Reports: Stewardship Report, Administering the National Federal-Aid Highway Program, 1972 May (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Reports: Sullivan and Montgomery, "Evaluating Highway Impacts,", 1972 September (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Reports: "Summary of Analysis and Recommendations on Alternate Proposals for DC Comprehensive Transportation Plan," supplement, 1968 November (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Reports: Survey of Public Opinion in DC Regarding New Freeways, 1969 March (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Reports: Trends Before Metrorail, 1982 July (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Reports: Tomorrow's Transportation, 1968 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Reports: The Urban Mass Transportation Administration, Circa 1968 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Reports: Urban Public Transportation, Selected References, 1966 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Reports: Urban Transportation Planning in the USA, An Historical Overview, US Department of Transportation, 1983 August (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Reports: WMATA Office of the Comptroller, Monthly Financial Report,[incomplete], 1968 December-1969 December (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Reports: WMATA Office of the Comptroller, Monthly Financial Report, [incomplete], 1970 January-1973 March (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Reports: WMATA "Resolution of the Board of Directors,", 1969 February (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Reports: WMATA, Treasurer's Reports, 1968 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - Oversized Reports: 1968 Estimate of the Cost of Completing the National System of Interstate and Defense Highways, 1967 August (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Oversized Reports: 1972 Estimate of the Cost of Completing the National System of Interstate and Defense Highways, 1971 August (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Oversized Reports: 1-266 Design Hearing Information, (copy 1), Circa 1966 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Oversized Reports: 1-266 Design Hearing Information, (copy 2), Circa 1966 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Oversized Reports: Washington Metropolitan Area Transportation Study, Volume I, 1950 (Box 78, Folder 5)